azcc.gov 2017-06-30

# Arizona Corporation Commission:

Privacy Policy Statement  
  
---  
Thank you for visiting the Arizona Corporation Commission web site and reviewing our Privacy Policy Statement. This policy statement is provided as required by statute to inform you about the information that may be collected as a result of your visiting our site. More importantly, we want you to know how that information may be used, and the steps we take to insure the security of your information. Your right to privacy is of utmost importance to the Arizona Corporation Commission and it is our desire to earn your trust and confidence when you conduct business with us via the internet.  
 **Online Customer Service and Alternatives**  
If you prefer to request information from us in person, you may do so by telephone or in person. Our goal here is to provide you with a more convenient and efficient means to interact with us.  
 **Collection and Use of Information**  
 _Information Collected and Stored Automatically by Cookies_  
The Arizona Corporation Commission may use "cookies" to gather information about your visit automatically in a standard log file. Cookies are simple test files stored on your computer by your web browser. The information we collect never identifies you personally and consists of only the following items:  
  
  1.  
The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "your school.edu" if you connect from a university's domain) from which you access the web site; 

  2. The IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access the web site; and

  3. The date and time of your access. 

We use this information to gather statistics about the amount of use the site receives. Again, we do not automatically record information about you as an individual. We do not share, sell, or otherwise disseminate the collected information.  
 _Information You Provide_  
Through our web site, you may request to be added to certain lists, or may complete forms for various purposes. As an alternative to completing the forms online, you may print the blank form, fill it out and mail it to us. Information we collect from you through the internet is treated the same as information you submit to us on a hard copy. In other words, much of the information you disclose to us becomes a matter of public record as required by law.  
If you choose to provide us with personal information we use that information to respond to your message and to help us get you the information you have requested. We only share the information you provide with another agency if your inquiry relates to that agency, or if required by law as outlined above.  
 **Security**  
We have taken several steps to safeguard the integrity of our computer systems and networks. These steps include, but are not limited to, individual authentication, the security of transmitted data, security monitoring, auditing, and encryption of your information. Security methods and measures have been integrated into the design, implementation and day-to-day practices of the entire government process.  
 **External Links Disclaimer**  
The Arizona Corporation Commission web site contains links to web sites operated by other entities. When you link to another site, you are no longer on the Arizona Corporation Commission's web site and this Privacy Policy Statement will not apply. When you link to another web site, you are subject to the privacy policy of that new site. These links are offered solely for your convenience and the State of Arizona is not responsible for and has no control over the policies or content of any third-party sites.  
 **Privacy Policy Statement Is Subject to Change**  
This policy may be updated or revised from time to time, so please check back with us periodically in order to receive advance notice of any substantive changes to the manner in which the information you disclose on this web site may be collected, used or disseminated.  
 **Contact Information**  
To offer comments about the Arizona Corporation Commission web site, or about the information presented in this Privacy Policy, please contact us:  
By email: 

By Telephone:

By Mail:

(602) 542-2237

Privacy Officer  
Arizona Corporation Commission  
1200 West Washington Street  
Phoenix, Arizona 85007
